[
    {
        "chapter": "Kinematics Introduction",
        "content": [
            {
                "question": "Mechanics is a branch of physics that explores the behavior of physical bodies influenced by forces or displacements.",
                "answer": ["True"],
                "difficulty": "Easy",
                "type": "TF",
                "students_answer": "True"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who among the following is known for significant contributions to classical mechanics?",
                "options": ["A. Albert Einstein", "B. Niels Bohr", "C. Isaac Newton", "D. Max Planck"],
                "answer": ["C. Isaac Newton"],
                "difficulty": "Easy",
                "type": "MCQ",
                "students_answer": "A. Albert Einstein"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of the following are fundamental concepts in mechanics?",
                "options": ["A. Space", "B. Time", "C. Mass", "D. Color"],
                "answer": ["A. Space", "B. Time", "C. Mass"],
                "difficulty": "Easy",
                "type": "MAQ",
                "students_answer": ["B. Time"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Mechanics is foundational in ______, astronomy, biology, and everyday life.",
                "answer": ["engineering"],
                "difficulty": "Medium",
                "type": "FITB",
                "students_answer": "engineering"
            },
            {
                "question": "If a car accelerates from rest to 20 m/s in 5 seconds, what is its acceleration? (Use a = Δv/Δt)",
                "answer": ["4 m/s²"],
                "difficulty": "Hard",
                "type": "NUMERICAL",
                "students_answer": "4"
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "chapter": "Kinematics Main",
        "content": [
            {
                "question": "Mechanics is a branch of physics that explores the behavior of physical bodies influenced by forces or displacements.",
                "answer": ["True"],
                "difficulty": "Easy",
                "type": "TF",
                "students_answer": "True"
            },
            {
                "question": "Who among the following is known for significant contributions to classical mechanics?",
                "options": ["A. Albert Einstein", "B. Niels Bohr", "C. Isaac Newton", "D. Max Planck"],
                "answer": ["C. Isaac Newton"],
                "difficulty": "Easy",
                "type": "MCQ",
                "students_answer": "C. Isaac Newton"
            },
            {
                "question": "Which of the following are fundamental concepts in mechanics?",
                "options": ["A. Space", "B. Time", "C. Mass", "D. Color"],
                "answer": ["A. Space", "B. Time", "C. Mass"],
                "difficulty": "Easy",
                "type": "MAQ",
                "students_answer": ["B. Time"]
            },
            {
                "question": "Mechanics is foundational in ______, astronomy, biology, and everyday life.",
                "answer": ["engineering"],
                "difficulty": "Medium",
                "type": "FITB",
                "students_answer": "life"
            },
            {
                "question": "If a car accelerates from rest to 20 m/s in 5 seconds, what is its acceleration? (Use a = Δv/Δt)",
                "answer": ["4 m/s²"],
                "difficulty": "Hard",
                "type": "NUMERICAL",
                "students_answer": "4"
            }
        ]
    }
]